and then we finally went to Barcelona for the weekend
went to a club and the rest is history
so he'd like drop me off then pick me up
ask me how it went but like the full on
like he wasn't bothered about having sex with anyone else
just wanted to watch me
gets a lot of his pleasure through pleasuring me
and watching me get pleasure from other people
yeah I'd
I do think like denial is a big part of
of cuckolding and I also find it
it's very hot denying a guy
especially when you can see how much they want it
we wanted to share that
you don't have to be ashamed of your sexual preferences
as long as everyone's happy
welcome to Cuckold Conversations presented by the Cuck Academy
I am Adriana Winters and in each episode
I'm going to be sitting down with real life
hot wife and cuckolding couples
together we are going to be exploring not just the kink
but the love
vulnerability and connection that makes their dynamic truly unique
whether you're curious experienced or somewhere in between
this is your space to hear authentic voices from inside the lifestyle
today I am joined by hot wife Alice
who some of you may recognize from uh
my very first ever Cuckold Confessions episode
welcome Alice
hi hello
um how are you
I'm good how are you
yeah very good
the sun is shining so it is
so I actually didn't see you that long ago
I think I saw you last month to film um
your second Coco Confessions episode
which was very hot I had a lot of fun filming that
it was so I'm gonna bring up some of that later yeah
that was gonna say kind of
both both born to do it aren't we now yes
so yeah I'm just gonna dive straight in uh
with some questions because yeah
I've I've worked with you a couple of times you and cookie um
but I'm quite excited to kind of delve a little bit deeper and kind of
find out a little bit more about your dynamic
and how you got there
we did a little bit the beginning of the second confessions
didn't we so yes
I'm excited I'm excited to see how that's come out
but um yeah
me too yeah
that's dropping uh in a month from where we are now
I don't know when this will be out
this will be yeah afterwards
but yeah watch this space everybody
exactly
it was so much fun that first cook old Confessions though
it was so yes so good yes
it's it's still my best seller
Yay mine too actually
yeah yeah yeah
it wasn't so filthy it was like yeah
and I don't think it was
because it was like the first time that cookie had done the buy stuff
like mm hmm
not ever we've done it a few times before
but on camera I don't know
like the setting like just the combination of all those four
the videographer yeah
it was just beautiful yeah
yes beautiful feels yeah
exactly
ha ha
okay so yeah
let's let's take it back a little bit and um
let's start with how did you and cookie meet originally
we met in a pub in Hackney
oh yeah
cool proper old school
and yeah when the Olympics was on in 2012 yeah
so I just graduated he was working in London
and we met at a dirty dive pub at about 2:00 o'clock in the morning
ah the best place to me yeah
I love that
so yeah and then we just like really got on
carried on dating and then about six months in
we made it official we're very
we're like slow burner yeah
it was good yeah
though yeah
I guess it's good if you're both on the same page with that slow burn
it gets a little bit yeah
if someone's moving at a different pace
and I think
because we've both been in quite intense relationships before
knew and knew what we then didn't want
yeah but yeah
it was a yeah
it was a slow it was a slow
slow start and now look at us
yeah and yes
and not a dating app which seems to be how most people meet these days
I know mad yeah
I also didn't meet my partner on a dating app
we also met in a pub so yeah
I'm here for a good old pub meeting
I know same
I'm like does it even happen anymore
a few of my friends are single and I'm like
I honestly like how do you even meet people nowadays
I mean when you're in this field it's very easy
but yeah
in actual life I'm like I have no idea
so would it be right to assume that Cuckolding wasn't on the table
right from the beginning of your relationship
no like we were both very sexually promiscuous
I would say in our past relationships
and then when we met as I said
like it was quite a slow burner
so we'd like meet up hook up
go on a date then not see each other for a bit and then
you know it was just like very chilled
um and then it was about a year in
I was on holiday actually
um with a few girlfriends and he text me
he was like I've um
I've just found this like website called fabs
do you remember fabs wiggers
yeah yeah
I used to have a profile on that yeah
same I think I still do somewhere if I've not been banned
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
um I was like right
um like a bit shocked
yeah because we've been so open
like we just spoke about everything
like he was married before like Day 3
he told me like there was just like no
nothing hidden kind of thing
so like anything we both said to each other was just like
we just took on board communicated
spoke about it and then just that was it kind of thing
so it's like a bit like oh
I'm not sure and then a year after that
I was like oh
let's do it I was like
let's do it yeah
um
because like we both knew that we found other people attractive
even though we were in a relationship
which is a very normal human thing
yeah to have um
some people don't act on it
some people do but the more we kind of spoke about like
oh he's fit or she's fit
like kind of like porn we were watching
then we kind of knew like the whole cheating thing
but obviously not lying to each other
cause we knew that we didn't want to do that either
and yeah it just kind of all built from there
and then we finally went to Barcelona for the weekend
went to a club and the rest is history
oh
um so like you said
you've been promiscuous in previous relationships
but I'm assuming that was without the other person knowing
it wasn't like an open relationship
well I did it once and then like
right I was about 19 at the time
and then told him the next
told him the next day as if like it wasn't a thing just like
well if I told him like
so then I think in my head I thought it's fine
like what what are you worried about
like it doesn't mean anything
it's just physical like I still love you
I just got a bit horny you know
so that was how my brain was working at 19
should have known that yeah
really shouldn't have yeah
um
and then him did he tell her
I'd I think like it was a bit of like hmm
it wasn't really working and then they both cheated kind of vibes
and then they didn't tell each other
but then it all came out and then that's why they broke up so
ah
yeah and so
so in Barcelona was it just you or cookie as well Connor
yeah so it was
it's called oops
it was a swinging like club
it's like a mansion I think
a house thing that
it's got a pool and a bar and a few different rooms
yeah and there was all different ages
it's like up on the hills
like looking over Barcelona
it's beautiful oh gorgeous
and there was a few older people there and then a few younger people
and we got invited into the VIP probably
cause we were like the youngest couple there
I bought yeah
exactly and then I just started sucking him off looking over Barcelona
um and then we went down to one of the rooms downstairs
and just kind of did stuff in a room in front of people
while other people were doing stuff more
a bit more like voyeurism
and then I just got really turned on and I was like yeah
this is this is the life for me
I can relate yup ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha um
so but the cook holding that didn't like the hot wife
then it was the hot wife in so so when we got back from Barcelona
we went back on fabs and there was this couple
they were great like super hot
and they were like well
you've been on here yeah
now if you don't come to this party on the weekend
then you won't be taken seriously
like basically might as well just delete your account right
so we then went to this party down in south London
and they were called Miss Decadence
they were great it was like at someone's house
they had a pool sauna hot tub steam room
it was like kind of went on all night
four different rooms to play in and met loads of people there
then went to heaven
where else to go then went to KV then to TG
and it just kind of all evolved from there over about a year or two OK
and then and it was mainly like couple like couple swap
but I kind of knew that he loved watching
more than actually doing anything
so then it was so then I'd start getting like with the single guys
or I'd just be more into like the girl and the guy
then he'd be watching
um
and yeah and then he was like
do you wanna go on like a date and just like not tell me
I was like yeah
why not sounds really fun
um and then that's when the hot
like proper hot wifeing started
so it'd like drop me off then pick me up
ask me how it went then like sometimes come in and join or
but most of the time then he'd start watching and like wanking
and then I think he bought a cage to start off with
I think he just wanted to like try it out and
and that's when like the full kind of
I mean hot wife and is still in
still cook holding isn't it
but like the full on
like he wasn't bothered about having sex with anyone else
just wanted to watch me
gets a lot of his pleasure through pleasuring me
and watching me get pleasure from other people
and then that's how that started
so and that was probably three years ago
okay yeah
yeah
I feel like you've been on my radio for like a couple of years now
so yeah I guess you started doing content quite soon after you kinda
well because of Covid
it was all right it was like
and then we had a little one
so it was a big break and then after Covid
I think I started the platform literally three years ago in March
so yeah exactly three years ago 2000
so you kind of discovered both at the same sort of time
you kind of was yeah
the most cool and stuff as I started on the platforms
but I don't know why I don't know why that was just pure coincidence
I think
because at the beginning I was always just like
just like the hot wife yeah
and he would join in more we do like couple swaps
but the more we got into it
it's like I'm just happy watching
it's so interesting isn't it how it progresses like that
I think for quite a lot of people uh yeah
I don't know why I feel like maybe the guys
uh don't feel that comfortable to say that they
maybe swinging is like more a easier kind of in
I think that yeah and because like
if you done it with an ex partner or in someone in the past
that maybe it would have been like
oh this is what I'm into and it would have been like from the start
but when I was only 23 he was 28 um
so I think back then
like you don't maybe you didn't even know you was into it
if you know what I mean like it just kind of yeah
evolved naturally together
cause I do get a lot of people on my sites like
how do I get my wife into it
how do I get my girlfriend into it
and I'm like if
if you've not discussed anything sexual like this before
that you just gotta start really slow
I was like
I don't know how else to say it you can't just go to be like
can you put a cage on me yeah yeah
I was actually listening to a episode of cut my life uh
last week and yeah there was a girl on there that was saying
she just discovered her partner's Tumblr profile
like back when Tumblr was a thing
and she found a picture of him in a cage on there
and that's how she discovered that that was his
his cage oh my God
that's so maybe just like yeah
and quite a few guys sort of say like
maybe they should just leave my
my book on their like coffee table or something and just see
see what happens see if that's a conversation starter or not
because I do get a lot of like husbands and partners and they're like
I just think she's like she's just really vanilla and I was like
but I was quite vanilla like 10 years ago fifth
well probably 15 years ago now
I was like but you just have to explore your sexual urges and not
and not be ashamed about it or feel bad about it
I think a lot of women like
I don't know just felt a bit scared to explore how sexually
promiscuously yeah
because you got called like a slut or a hoe or whatever
which is ridiculous because I mean
yes yes
yeah I think we
I mean obviously I fantasize
I'm sure you do too but I feel like not as often as men do
so I think men are just like in their head a lot more
just be like thinking about these kinks and yeah
and things and I don't think we spend as much time being like oh
fantasizing yeah
I agree and I think for a woman
it's a lot more of an emotional thing
yeah so I'm intrigued actually
you mentioned that cookie said um
go and go on a date so I hear a lot that guys say that
and then when it actually comes down to it
they freak out and they're sending like
a million text messages and phone calls
and like did you
did that happen with you guys
or was did he actually just leave you to it
no he left me to
he did drop me off and then he left us to it
and then came like three or four hours later or whatever
but I think he wasn't
he wasn't like constantly on me because we'd met this guy at a club
like three or four times before
OK so he knew you were safe and so he see
he knew I was safe and um
and had nothing to worry about basically
yeah but yeah
I guess but now he loves it if it's just a random date
as long as I'm safe I have to update him and tell him where I am
or just leave my live location on yeah
that's good good tip
yeah
that's literally is only boundary
as long as she's safe
like that is his only do whatever you want as long as you say yeah
like yeah
that's great um
and like what's
I guess that kind of brings us onto like
what's your like vetting of new guys
like I guess it makes sense if you can meet guys in like public spaces
at play parties and stuff
but if that's not the case
like what's the process
I literally ask them for their ID
yeah I mean
but I guess there's a lot of people that won't
that won't do that but I guess that just
but then but then that just
that I just don't meet yeah
exactly cause I'm like
if you if you
if I'm gonna give someone my body
I'm like deserve to know who you are yeah
yeah I'm quite frankly yeah
and then that whittles out a hell of a lot of people yeah
but you're yeah
you're not left wasting your time on people um
that yeah
interesting cause I think a lot of people have the fantasy about like
getting with a hot wife but actually
they wanna pretend they're someone else while they're doing it
maybe if it's a bit of a fantasy and I'm
I'm just like I don't have time for that yeah
it's about me not you
classic hot wife ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
um so what do you personally enjoy about the cuckolding dynamic
ah ah
it's just so liberating
mm hmm um
like the connection that you get as a couple
I think a lot of it is actually then explain like going back to cookie
talking about what I got up to
like seeing how happy he is and how turned on he is yeah
and I do just love massive
yeah me too
my old podcast was Size Queen
it was purely focused on size Queen
so uh
yeah
ha ha which cookie
it's got a very average you know yeah
penis but yeah
the average isn't enough for size queen
no ha ha that that's like great for home life
I mean I mean
not that we have we do it very much anymore with each other
um things have evolved
but back then you know
everyday everyday prettiness
but now it's just I think it's just
it is the honesty and the trust that you have to put in someone
and the relationship that I think actually just makes my heart melt
as well as you know what I mean
yeah
yeah I guess it
just makes the relationship stronger
because if you're like that open and that trusting in each other
in that dynamic you just can't hide anything
yeah so there is none of that
what if kind of thoughts that I think a lot of people end up having
yeah so did this dynamic make you feel like empowered straight away
or did that kind of confidence builds over time
I think yeah
the confidence just built over time
I mean I was as wide as I was tall when I was like a teenager
oh and then lost
lost loads of weight um
like just in the elder teenage
elder teenagers like into my 20s and at uni
and then I think it just built from there
like I got in shape started going to the gym
and then with like the dating and then just being naked in a
in a in a swinging club just feels great
like it's so empowering yeah
um
and I think yeah
it was just a slow burner
like to be fair
I've been brought up to like love my body and who I am and like
which is which is great and
but it does definitely build the confidence
it was over time for sure
yeah and do you find that like uh
the content and stuff that you films also kind of built
built your confidence as well
yeah like some people can't even watch their own content back
I'm like I love watching mine
I'm having a play at the same time watching it back
I don't know what you call that side
yeah yeah yeah
I don't know I'm sure there is a word for it um
but yeah yeah
I can't remember but like yeah
I'm not ashamed about what I look like my body and I think yeah
I think filming yourself and looking back does
does help you like oh
that's a good angle oh
I need to do that again yeah yeah
but also I try not to I try not to think about it too much
cause I do like it to be as natural as possible yeah
um and I think in this industry
is hard to kind of not be a bit critical of
my mum told me or my arm here
or my chin here but I think like I've been through it
no one's looking at your chin
are they when they're no literally I'm just
I'm 36 now I'm over it
I'm like this is me
take it or leave it
you go find someone else if you don't if you don't find it hot
I'm honestly not bothered
but yeah it's like
I think confidence comes with age as well
doesn't it as you as you get older yeah
so what surprised you the most uh
when you started uh exploring cuckolding
like you said in like when he mentioned fabs like back then you
you weren't sure so like what's
what surprised you the most
I was just like well excited yeah
I was like it was like a new toy
it was like a kid at Christmas
I was like ooh
um and I think
because obviously it came from him in the first place to try it yeah
um and then for me
it became like a bit of an addiction of like
the denial and teasing him um
like I do get a massive like thrill of that yeah
endorphin and adrenaline rush like yeah
it's like he is actually locked away like he can't
he has no choice now basically yeah
when he wants to pleasure himself so
yeah I
I do think like denial is a big part of
of cuckolding and I also find it very hot denying a guy
especially when you can see how much they want it and you're like no
and you can see how much more that just gets them even more yeah
it literally and I think it's like a bit of a worshipping thing
isn't it I mean
like who doesn't want to be worshipped
but like for our whole relationship
he's always like worship the ground I walk on
this was just like I don't know yeah
he's cute he does get loud occasionally
I can't pretend is in it 100% of the time 95% yeah
I mean this is not practical
is it like you yeah
but um
but yeah yeah
I don't
don't believe people when they're like tweet locked all the time
I also think it kind of gives people a of the
just the wrong impression of like
how like you gotta take off to clean it and just yeah
I think yeah it's just not
there's a lot of maintenance
and it takes ages to find one to get that actually fits yeah
to be honest yeah yeah um
so yes it is a process
it is like anything in life though
I just like I think that's why we first started cause I was like
it was kind of we'd had loads of videos obviously from swinging
but just for like personal like
I don't know when we're older we're like oh
we're gonna look at this when we're 17 and be like
oh we had a great life
so what was it that made you start filming it
was it just like the swinging couples that you were around or
yeah like
I've actually have been filming myself
and boyfriends and taking pictures since like
I first have a phone at like 18
so yeah like
and I think it was someone we met in the industry as like
at a swinging party and they just kind of suggested it
so I started my Twitter just cause I
and I did have a Tumblr back in the day
so we're on five and I started a bit of a Tumblr
but then I think Tumblr went down
I can't remember what happened
they banned all the adult content in there
yeah which is all it was 2000
what we have now 2006
like 2,018 17 yeah
maybe I can't remember
yeah it was definitely good few years ago
so I never really thought anything of it
and then it was a friend in the swinging scene that was like
why don't you start a Twitter
so I did and then after Covid and the little one like growing up a bit
um and just like job wise
um I was like
you know I've got a bit of extra time to like see if this kind of
I can make something of this
yeah and yeah
it was a bit of a slow burner too
like but I don't like rushing into stuff
so yeah I'm
and I still do test the water
yeah test the water
I'm still doing like my design job now freelance
like I like having my fingers in lots of pies
um
so yeah and then it just kind of grew from there
and was it quite nerve wracking putting like your relationship online
not really I think like my
like cookie was the one that kind of was always saying
don't worry about it like this is who we are
like we don't need to be ashamed
like he's just great like that
and every time I'm having a moment
it's like
we're adults like we're just having a bit of horny fun like it's fine
yeah all consensual
it's all consensual yeah
exactly like we're all adults um
and I think then like as that got into my head
I was like okay
maybe we should start stop
should start sharing this because then like
people won't be as ashamed
like I was like
there wasn't there was a few cuckolding people out there
but I was like the hot wife thing
but I was like yeah
let's just start and share and see see how it goes
I think that's the most exciting part for me is just seeing how much
cause I started shooting cuckolding content
I guess like 10 years ago yeah
you must have been like one of the first um
and yeah it's just so exciting
how was it back then was like
I mean I didn't really I know much about it
I guess it was my partner that got me into it and yeah
he just happened to be a camera guy as well
so like yeah he would just film me with other guys
and I guess
we didn't lean into it as being cockold in quite such an obvious way
but that's very much what it was and um
yeah um
it's just so nice to see how much it's grown over the last 10 years
and I love it when people message me being like
it's your content that inspired me us to get into it and I'm like yay
I just
and the same as you
that's I just want less people to be ashamed of it and just embrace it
yeah and I just think like anything sexual
as long as it's consensual
you're not hurting anyone
like you shouldn't be ashamed
I think like even when we were like growing up as teenagers
it was so hard to like navigate like who you were
what you liked
like you get made fun of if you said that you played with yourself
which is just you know what I mean
I just think like obviously everything has to be age appropriate
it's fine the boys too though
yeah the yeah exactly what the hell
same with the same with the hoe though
isn't it like boys are allowed to be hoes but girls aren't
yeah but I think things are changing finally but
yes um
but yeah I think we just started sharing because at like 1
it felt very liberating and 2
we wanted to share that
you don't have to be ashamed of your sexual preferences
as long as everyone's happy
yes so
uh I mentioned
um before that um yeah
the last time I met you um
we filmed a very well actually both the scenes we've done
um
have been kind of exploring cookies by side
so um
yeah I mean that's something I don't
I just find it really hot just watching guy on guy action
I don't know what it is I think
I don't know if it's because I'm such a straight woman
that I'm just not really that interested in watching
watching a woman I'd rather just watch two two men
and you know what that's definitely like evolved from me
when we were swinging like a few years in
we met this couple and the girl
the girlfriend really got turned on by the guys doing stuff
and we've never done anything like that before yeah
um but we had a little chat
like went
nipped the way we went for dinner and nipped to the bathroom
had a little chat I was like yeah
if you wanna do it like just try it like what's the worst
like you know
might as well yeah
um and then he did it and the girl was loving it
I was just like a bit nothing he about it was just like
didn't love it didn't hate it like it was just what
I don't know it was and then he was like
it's like putting a like a sausage in your mouth hahaha
I was like didn't really turn me on blah blah blah
this was like 10 like eight years ago and then that was that
I was like OK
he's not really that bothered yeah
um but then I think as we got more into the cook holding and the like
submissive and like the denial
and then like the pleasure um
then it just it just kind of happened naturally um
and I'm there like yeah
ha ha now I'm the now I'm the boy
I'm like the one watching how the tables have turned yeah oh
cause he he uh
it strikes me as someone that quite likes the kind of service
role of it so yeah
like just just kind of helping your experience by
by kind of getting involved and and
and then sharing with you yeah
and like obviously emotionally behind
behind the scenes that no one really let me do see
but he was he's just like
I love that it turns you on and it's like yeah
it is servicing and pleasuring you and your balls so yeah
that's kind of where the mind um yeah
the mindset is cause I was like
you fancy just going to took someone off like without me
it's like no
that's not that's not that's not what he finds hot about it it's like
yeah what he finds hot about it is like
the emotional and the sexual kind of service
I suppose yeah
yeah I can see that um
so um
yeah I was gonna ask who bought it up
but I guess it just happened at this
this club that you were just kind of presented with the opportunity
and you went for it yeah
yeah um yeah
back in the day yeah
hundred percent and then how did it come up again
the second time
like when he actually started like doing more couple swap stuff
uh do
uh exploring his bi side a bit more like
oh OK
further I'm like
I can't actually remember how
obviously it was like the hot wife in the cage
but actually I think maybe we just met someone who was into it
and we were yeah
and we were both really horny
and then we just tried it and then liked it
like there I don't think there was any discussion
there wasn't like we were
we hadn't started watching like adult content like that
it literally yeah
happened really naturally
and then obviously
then we met the guy that did the first cook old confessions mm hmm
and he was into it and then yeah
that was it then met um
Montreal
then Headingley so much
he's such a babe isn't it
honestly I absolutely adore him
oh he's just great
cause I think he was like a bit like
sensitive to share it to start off with
and I was like honestly
like who
who gives a fuck
I was like
um I think unfortunately there's still a lot of societal stigma
yeah stigma around it
which is a shame uh
cause yeah like
cause girls ironically I think it's like girls are allowed to be bi
yeah exactly
you kind of almost expected to be as someone that
that is very much straight
I'm like no
I do not want no interest
stop it stop assuming that I'm going to
ha ha
but yeah oh
it's the complete opposite
like women it's just like
oh yeah women are just always just like getting off with each other
it's fine but men
oh gosh no
oh my god yeah
I was getting off with my friends when I was like 16
God oh this
I was born for this life wasn't I
I was used to joke cause I used to do girl girl like for porn studios
and I used to joke that I was just doing gay for pay
it was just
I mean there's a big niche there so yeah
an untapped niche I would say yeah
um
so yeah it would just all happen naturally
I don't know if this is a risky question
uh based on your reactions when I've kind of touched on it already
but what goes through your mind when uh
you watch him with another man
I I just feel so much love
ha ha ha oh
I don't have proper soppy in my old age
no obviously extremely horny
and I just I do love the
that's what makes me horny
I love the fact that like he can just be himself
like we're doing it together
and yeah that's not really much more else to say apart from like
he does look adorable when he's doing it
he does look good doing it
I have to say he's got a lot better as well
ha ha ha ha ha yeah
I'm teach train training him
well teaching him yes
cause those are some big
those are some big members that it can fit in there now
so yes yeah
yeah we'd haven't uh
started him on a entry level yeah um
um
yeah I guess
I guess the dynamic for you guys is
is like the fact that you're got guiding him to it
that's I guess that's the kind of yeah
spice that's needed for it to be to work for you guys
yeah
um
and I suppose like it just kind of felt the most like the most natural
I don't even know yeah
it was just felt really natural
it looks natural you
you guys yeah
yeah
and um
you've also introduced some pegging as well
yes a little bit
we we actually used to do it a bit more
um
and then we stopped for a while and I was like off camera or on camera
um or both
I've not actually pegged him properly on camera yet
oh well
I'm privileged that I got that opportunity
hopefully I didn't uh scar him too much
no it's fine
we've done it off we've done it off camera
fab like we did it quite a bit
and then like stopped and then he got more into like the sucking yeah
um
and then he kind of like got into it a bit more
so I've got literally like one three minute video on my page
like of of us just messing about like
you know it's like pouring the light into rubbish
yeah yeah
um so I do actually need to get a proper
a proper what a proper it's quite hard to film POV like yeah
I tried doing it you just set up like a tripod
it's so hard yeah
uh it's much easier when you have a camera guy to kind of
make sure they get in the ankles
but yeah it's not easy POV um
so on on camera I've not I have not pegged him that much
but in obviously in our personal life I've done it for a few times
we've just never had managed to get it on camera properly
I've I've done it with a lot
obviously we did um
Nelly's cook at the Content Weekend
yes and I did it with Ruby and yup with another cook few months ago
um but yeah
I'll make that I'll I'll make it a thing for this year to get a proper
yeah my favourite
like particular little thing is when they're in chastity
and you're pegging them yeah
that's that's a really good of course yeah
um but yeah
I guess people listening to this will have to let
you know if it's something they wanna see
um yeah
I do get asked for it quite a lot
oh okay
but just because I do like to do things natural
I'm like look
like I've just not got round to setting up my lighting when I do it
you know yeah yeah
but I will do eventually
oh well
as fun as it's been discussing cookies by side
let's change change the subject
um what
he's had enough attention now yes
it's just me being indulgent in a
in a kink that I particularly enjoy
so yeah
so you so you really enjoy watching it as well
yes yeah
very much so yeah
um there's just something about it
I can't I can't put my finger on it
I just it just makes me feel great
ha ha ha so ha ha ha so um yeah
let's move on to um
what do you think people misunderstand the most about cock holding
oh God that's such a hard one
I think a bit of a misconception is that like
it comes from a like controlling angle
or it has to always be about humiliation
cause mine and cookies is like the complete opposite of that yeah um
what else that they're
that they're always like a bit dweeby and a bit geeky or a bit fat
yeah
that is how porn portrays cocks
yeah just yeah
I'm like fat little
and I think that's probably why we're so like adamant about sharing it
it's like you can still be really hot yourself
be in good shape like be a normal human in
society and still like being a cook like yeah exactly yeah
uh yeah
it's interesting what you say about the control thing
cause I do think that is genuinely a problem sometimes um
yes
um but yeah
the more and more I you know
I meet you and and other women I'm like yeah
no you're definitely fully in this
it's not your partner being like
go and do this for me and you just being no
it's okay if it makes you happy
yeah it literally just comes
I don't even know what the word is
but like it comes from sharing rather than control
like yeah
it's not obviously like we'd get he gets
he does get a bit jealous
but like he said at the beginning of the second cook or confessions
like he likes that jealousy like yeah
it doesn't it doesn't make him insecure
it doesn't make him feel sad
like a load of people hate jealousy like makes them feel like awful
whereas he like actually thrives on it a little bit is like yeah yeah
look at look at my wife
ha ha ha yeah
like that he gets a real sense of satisfaction from a bit of jealousy
yeah um
so it's not coming from a controlling environment
yeah it's more pride and yeah
that kind of yeah
which is yeah yeah yeah yeah
the next question was
do people assume that you're being forced into it
and we we did we
literally discovered that
so that's good I think we can go into that a bit more though
like at the beginning when I'd open up to like my
like family and friends to be like
they be like oh
he's having his cake and eating it
oh he's making you do it
and then like
the more they got to know our dynamic and our relationship
they were like absolutely not
I think that is a misconception as well
yeah
but I was I was like
really not and
and then now look you know
like we're both just genuinely happy
like there's no it's not
there's no like it's
it's all equal it's not like we're doing it to like
get something over on someone or like
try and make someone jealous or it's like
oh yeah coming from a very mutual grounding
which I think a lot of misconception about
maybe swinging or cuckolding or
I don't know the lifestyle is that like
it always comes from one person and a bit of control
which actually I mean
maybe that is the case in some situations
but I I don't
I just don't think this kind of relationship lasts if there's
yeah there needs to be that respect
yeah there needs to be yeah
respect is basically like the biggest thing
uh I think
my favourite
word that I've Learned in the last few years is compersion
which is when someone gets off on someone else's satisfaction yeah
and I feel like both of you are like that
like you enjoy knowing that he's having a good time
and he really gets off on knowing that you're having a good time
and if that's not there then it's not working for either of you
like no yeah
which I hear a lot yeah it's definitely
definitely quite a common thing yes
um
so um
I feel like you guys have already explored quite a lot in the
in the last couple of years
but where do you see your dynamic evolving next
I've literally I don't even know if there is anywhere
I know this is what I was thinking
I was thinking this the other day
I was like
because in the last year obviously
we've explored the more cuckolding and by side
and I'm like because we've done it
like you said like
where did that come from I'm like
I literally couldn't tell you
it wasn't like a defining moment
obviously cage
he brought a cage he bought a cage
he ordered a cage and it arrived one day
like that obviously yeah
um but everything else has just been so natural
that I literally have no idea
like we just kind of like to keep it as natural as possible
and basically we're just gonna
we'll just see what happens
who knows yeah
I kind of like that you're just kind of presented with opportunities
and you kind of just check in with each
other and decide if you're gonna go for it and then you're like
yeah OK cool
let's but I
let's try this that is honestly like years of swinging at the start
like yeah
we'd always make sure that like afterwards
or even that night and then the next morning
like we'd always check in what we did like what we didn't like um
not even in terms of like sexual stuff
but like feelings um
and so I think now
we can just look at each other and don't know what we're thinking
which is like which is like
I mean yeah
I'm very lucky like I am
yeah my soulmate
so yeah I know it was meant to be whatever happens who knows
we keep talking about going to live in another country
so we'll see you
oh I'd also love to do that
um yeah
uh
yeah I don't even know
I don't even know if any like if this question uh
needs asking but
are there any fantasies that you're still excited to explore together
like is there still anything that you're like oh
I I think we just like found our little thing
you know it's not yeah
little is it but I think we just like found what we like
and yeah that's if it's not broke
if it ain't broke don't fix it or whatever the expression is
no we just yeah
exactly we found your little
yeah I think he with like
life's been so busy just in general life
and I think he would like me to go like actually properly cheat
you know go get on a dating app
find someone I do that occasionally
but like it's just kind of taken a bit of a backseat recently
and it's effort isn't it
cause you just got so many time wasters
and then it's just not fun because yeah
cause it's just more admin
yeah I'm like
I just wanna get stretched out
yeah um
but yeah sometimes I need to like
form some sort of like bull directory of just like vetted
you know men that are just available for
for dates uh
with with minimal vet vetting on there with yeah
like Hot Wives part yeah
Adriana approved
yeah part of the fun is kind of like getting to know someone a bit
yeah so yeah yeah
so I probably should make some more conscious effort to that
but like as soon as I'm having so much fun
we've been able to film the stuff and then I do have like a few um
I can't what what's the word what it is
but um
guys on the side like that I've known for a while
um yeah
but I just see them like every
every so often so I have one final question for you um
if another couple was curious about cuckolding
what advice would you give them
go for it yes
you'll never look back
I love that I think like
I do find this like really hard question to answer
because ours happened so slowly that I don't yeah
I hate saying I'll just go for it and then you scare someone
and I don't like I'm like
I don't wanna ruin any relationships
I just wanna make them better
and yeah
so maybe my advice is a bit slower than some
like someone else's advice
but yeah I just think like go for it
the first thing I say if someone's like comes to my page is like
I really wanna get into it
I'm like if you've never done anything like this before
just make a date night into a swinging club and just go like yeah
what's the worst there's like no pressure to do anything
you can no pressure to do anything
it's literally like go out for a nice dinner
check out the club for a few hours
like you don't that you don't have to buy a cage
put it on
and sit there and tell your partner to stamp all over your balls
you know like it's like that doesn't have to yeah
you've got a like baby steps
baby steps yeah
um
but I guess like you said from the beginning
like communication is is everything
so you kind of need to have that foundation
you've got to learn yeah
you've got to obviously a lot of couples communicate great
but this is like a totally
different unlocked kind of
you do have to be so honest with you
it's like an emotional
like huge emotional intelligence to even talk about these
this kind of thing
so I think you've got to build that first before you yeah
I mean if you've got that anyway
great like to say whatever um yeah
you can take it in the right way
ha ha
um
but I think it depends it's like
it's so individual isn't it
but obviously cause of my background and my understanding of it all
like and cause it was quite a slow burner
that is where I'd go I'd be like
yeah go for it
but I would just go easy yeah
if they've not done anything before
obviously if they've been in relationships before where it's
um
where they've explored that kind of dynamic or some sort
some part of it yeah
and I think also like
if you have been married like 20 years
and you really don't think your wife or your husband's into it
like sexual preferences change so much over time
like you're not the same person that when you met them 10
25 years ago and so
I think a lot of people would be surprised
if they actually did have that honest conversation
what reaction they'd get like
especially if you get into your late 30s
40s 50s
I think people are a lot more kind of willing to explore
and yeah and I think also
what just popped into my head is
you know I've heard from you and I've heard from like Q s
Lucy and just you know
other people online that quite often the first time it gets brought up
isn't the time isn't the time no
um and quite often it's a year or two down the line yeah
so like for your partner to be like
this is fab swingers and you to be like
oh I don't know yeah
it's be like a year before you kind of came back to it
just kind of yeah
thinking about it and yeah
I hear I hear that a lot that like it gets put out there
doesn't land but then yeah
I think we watched like I was like OK yeah
like let's look into it and then we watched like a vice documentary
I think it was like
filming a bit of heaven and what not back in the day
and like yeah
everyone had all the masks on
and I was like yeah
oh I don't know
just looks just I don't know
I'm just like no
this isn't really turning me on
and then a year later I'm like
let like it was his
it was actually his birthday
so we went to Barcelona it was like different city
it looked like a nice like club
I was like do you know what
like then that then I was like in the mood to try it then
I was like what's the worst that's gonna happen
and then we loved it so I do yeah
I just think like
like you've got like time
time's just everything
hmm
so I'm gonna start wrapping things up now
is there anything else you wanna add
or anything you wanna let people know about any like
content you've got coming out or you have
have the mic for well
it depends when this podcast comes out
we do we've obviously got the new cook old confessions
we've got the yes yes
which I'm very excited about
um me too
it was so hot yeah
literally I'm so excited
I can't wait to I can't wait to see it
um which is what we are now March
so that's the end of April um
yeah I've got another like double by cook one coming out in
in a few weeks I think um
I've started doing all my compilations
which I love because I was like
just seeing it all in one movie is so hot
oh well
thank you so much for chatting to me today
it's a no
thank you it's been so lovely
just yeah
uh digging a little bit deeper and um yeah
hopefully like what you've shared will inspire other people or
you know just inspire
yeah or just
you know help them to feel less
less shame around what what they're thinking or feeling
so 100% yeah
that's all that's I think that's why that's
literally all that's just makes me happy every day
any fan that comes to me is like
you've made me feel less ashamed
I'm like this is
this is my job well done
not that I'll see it as like me too
you know
I don't see it as a job cause I love it even though it is a job
um
but yeah it makes
makes me happy me too
and I can be filthy at the same time
so it's great you've been listening to Cuckold
Conversations brought to you by The Cuck Academy
if you have enjoyed today's episode
follow the podcast and leave a review
it helps more people discover the lifestyle
for resources guides and courses on cuckolding
visit the Cuck academy.com
until next time keep the conversation going